warriorplus.com 2018-08-09

# Privacy Policy | WarriorPlus

WarriorPlus.com ("Site" or "WarriorPlus") cares about your privacy. Actually our lawyer made us say that, since all internet marketers are little data hoarders. Anyway, we collect personal information that may be used for many purposes, including, but not limited to, product and service fulfillment, to communicate with members and potential members of our website, and to make it a better online experience for all of our users. We may allow some third-party advertisers ("third party" or "third parties") to collect and use personal information for many purposes including fulfilling WSO orders, or sending you to a third party page to view their offers. These advertisers may have a separate privacy policy to cover the use of this information on their separate websites which you are responsible for.

Information that you provide to us - "Personal Information"

Portions of the site may require you to create and an account and provide certain personal information. Including your name, address, email, telephone, company name, paypal account, credit card information, Warrior Forum account, and other information as needed.

We may also enable Site users and visitors to provide additional information via surveys, reviews, WSO alerts, and actions that may require them to express their interest in certain products. In addition, all personal information or content that is publicly posted or otherwise disclosed, either publicly or privately, by way of usage of the Site may be collected. 

Cookies

The Site uses both "session ID cookies" and "persistent cookies." Session cookies are used to make it easier for users to navigate the Site. A session ID cookie expires when the users' browser is closed. Persistent cookies enable the Site to monitor and target the interests of its users for an enhanced experience on the Site. Your web browser enables you to view and control the cookies on your computer. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use the Site, but your ability to use some areas or functionality of the Site may be reduced.

We use cookies to allow you to log in to our service, authenticate your Salesforce account, verify certain information about you, and to record session information. You may be required to have cookies turned on when integrating your Salesforce account with our Platform. While you do not necessarily have to have permanent cookies enabled, it does help us with distinguishing you from other users, and protecting your security and privacy. We also reserve the right to use cookies, web beacons, or web bugs to track the success of our marketing efforts. Again, while we do not plan to use certain cookies right now we reserve the right to use these cookies to tell us what sites you have visited, but we only use this information in conjunction with our Service and related marketing efforts. 

Email Inquiries

WarriorPlus may collect information when you email us. In addition, if you sign up for our WSO Alerts you agree to receive emails about the latest WSO's, or information about any of your orders. You accept full responsibility for referring pages or email to anyone, and will do so in full compliance with any applicable CAN-SPAM or privacy laws.

Information Collected by our ISP

We may employ third party companies and individuals to perform tasks or operate our servers. These third parties may have access to your information for the purpose of performing those tasks, and are restricted from disclosing or using it for any other purpose. The hosting provider for this Site has the ability to record various pieces of information, including domain name, pages accessed, date and time of access, web browser type and computer operating system, as well as referring information. This information is stored in our server logs and may be accessible to us from time to time.

HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

By registering as a user, or otherwise contacting the Site for the purposes of becoming a user, you intentionally consent to receiving communications from us via email, telephone, SMS, or any other delivery method. In providing personal information to us for the purposes of creating your user account or setting up your WSO Plus account, or through contacting us with the intent of becoming a user you acknowledge that we may communicate with you via email, internal Site messaging services, or other means of communication that you have provided us including mobile text messages. Please be advised that if we send communications to any mobile phones or other devices you understand and agree that you will pay for any such service fees associated with receipt of messages on such device (including text messages).

The Site may also send you information that will enhance your user experience in addition to promotional information directly or on behalf of other users, sellers, or partners of WarriorPlus. Unless otherwise notified, certain information may be shared with other users of the site internally or externally. The Site may also use this information to help improve or promote the Site and/or our partners' sites. 

WarriorPlus may also contact you with service-related announcements, as well as alerts about the latest WSO's, also use your registered name and email address to inform you about significant announcements regarding Site functions and services that you are registered to use, about the Site, about any user account you may create, about fulfillment of a specific transaction you have requested, or about other significant developments that may affect your use of the Site. Users cannot opt-out of service-related announcements.

Release of Information for Legal Reasons

We may release information concerning your use of the Site, Platform and when we believe in good faith that such release is appropriate to comply with the law or to protect ourselves (yea we'd throw you under the bus like that if you were defrauding us). 

Transfer of information

We may transfer your information in the event we are bought, sold, or a substantial portion of our assets are acquired. 

Data Security and Risks inherent with information sharing

No security measures are perfect. There can be no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by any breach of any physical, technical, or other safeguards. Nor can we guarantee that any information that you share on the Site or with other users will not become publicly available. You assume all responsibility and liability for the use or misuse of your personal data, including the use of such data by others that use such information in an inappropriate way or that may cause you harm. 

International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside of the United States, you are consenting to the transfer of your information outside of your country into the US and vice versa. 

A NOTE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS (ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 2003 - OPPA)

WarriorPlus intends to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579, created by the Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003. If you are a California resident, you can request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Act. To obtain information about our Privacy collection practices in regard to California law, you may request a copy of our privacy information free of charge once per year. To obtain our privacy information please email us at privacy@warriorplus.com.

Amendments

The "Amendments" paragraph of our Terms of Service is hereby incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy and applies to any amendments that we may make to this Privacy Policy.
